<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Random Ramblings</title>
		<description>Just some space where I pour my heart out. Suganthi's personal space</description>
		<link>enthudrives.me</link>
		<atom:link href="enthudrives.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#39;ll find this post in your &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory - edit this post and re-build (or run with the &lt;code&gt;-w&lt;/code&gt; switch) to see your changes!
To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention: YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;Tom&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &amp;#39;Hi, Tom&amp;#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mojombo/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll&amp;#39;s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 21:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2014/02/12/welcome-to-jekyll</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2014/02/12/welcome-to-jekyll</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>A peek into the year that passed by</title>
				<description>Though 2013 started off quiet, with me sitting idle in my flat, it turned out to be quite an eventful year.

Just like anyother year, 2013 was filled with ups and downs. But looking back, I had a great year. A lot of firsts happened in 2013.

Here's my first bike. Honda Activa.

[caption id=&quot;&quot; align=&quot;aligncenter&quot; width=&quot;150&quot;]&lt;img alt=&quot;Honda Activa&quot; src=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BJl-pcJCAAEWz4o.jpg:thumb&quot; width=&quot;150&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt; My first bike[/caption]

Had my first accident as well. Phew :P

Took swimming membership in Aquatic Complex. Its a 7 feet deep, 50 metres long pool. Went swimming for 1.5 months in a row, after which I moved to Pune for a Project.

Pune is a lovely city. The weather is pleasant. Drive 2 hours towards any direction and you'll reach a nice hilly village from which you can trek to one of Shivaji's forts. That inspired me to visit as many forts possible before I leave Pune.

&lt;a href=&quot;http://tsuganthi.files.wordpress.com/2014/01/2013-07-13-14-27-33.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;aligncenter size-medium wp-image-578&quot; alt=&quot;2013-07-13 14.27.33&quot; src=&quot;http://tsuganthi.files.wordpress.com/2014/01/2013-07-13-14-27-33.jpg?w=300&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;51&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;

My first trek(in my whole life) was to Rajmachi. That's the longest trek in 2013 as well. Walked 28 kms in total that day. When we reached the Lonavala railway station after the trek, I was walking like a donald duck :P . This trek was followed by a lot more forts.. Pratapghad, Rajghad, Tikona are some other b-e-a-utiful forts that I visited around Pune.

Apart from forts, I also visited some beautiful touristy locations like Mahabaleshwar, Kaas Plateau.

&lt;img class=&quot;aligncenter size-medium wp-image-579&quot; alt=&quot;IMG_0009&quot; src=&quot;http://tsuganthi.files.wordpress.com/2014/01/img_0009.jpg?w=300&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;199&quot; /&gt;

I went there in the 1st weekend of September. That's the right time to be there. Flowers had just blossomed and the place looked like a pink carpet with patterns on it.

The most adventurous day of my life was also in 2013. Went Valley crossing &amp;amp; Rappelling at Duke's nose in Lonavala.

[caption id=&quot;attachment_580&quot; align=&quot;aligncenter&quot; width=&quot;200&quot;]&lt;a href=&quot;http://tsuganthi.files.wordpress.com/2014/01/img_3156.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;size-medium wp-image-580&quot; alt=&quot;Spot me in the picture&quot; src=&quot;http://tsuganthi.files.wordpress.com/2014/01/img_3156.jpg?w=200&quot; width=&quot;200&quot; height=&quot;300&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Spot me in the picture[/caption]

Trekked to a 1000 feet high cliff and rappelled down 600 feet. Climbing 600 feet up was an add-on which was hidden in this package. As it had rained the previous night, the rocks were slippery and stones were rolling down. It was a bit scary, but totally worth it.

[caption id=&quot;&quot; align=&quot;aligncenter&quot; width=&quot;104&quot;]&lt;img alt=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;http://m.ak.fbcdn.net/sphotos-d.ak/hphotos-ak-frc3/p480x480/1458440_10151836508688019_1037353607_n.jpg&quot; width=&quot;104&quot; height=&quot;138&quot; /&gt; Finished 8km run[/caption]

Another achievement in 2013 is, I ran an 8 km Marathon. Yet another 1st in my life. Will definitely continue running in 2014 as well :)

Also, played Tennis, went ice skating(a small rink in Inorbit mall) for the first time.

There were quite a few, 1st of a kind, sad moments as well. But, looking back, none of it matters :)

Such an eventful year it was. Special thanks to all my friends who stayed by my side &amp;amp; shared my happiness and sorrows.  :)

Happy New Year 2014 :)
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2014/01/03/a-peep-into-the-year-that-passed-by</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2014/01/03/a-peep-into-the-year-that-passed-by</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>F.R.I.E.N.D.S</title>
				<description>FRIENDS is my most favourite sitcom so far. I never thought that I could get addicted to this sitcom. Because, I had a problem with those random voices which laugh hysterically in the middle of a conversation. But later, my brain found its way to filter out those laughters from bothering my system. I tried to start watching many times. But failed right at the Season1 Episode1.

I got a very good tip from a friend. Start watching from the 3rd season. Because the first 2 seasons are mostly to break the ice among those 6 characters. It did work!

[caption id=&quot;&quot; align=&quot;alignnone&quot; width=&quot;691&quot;]&lt;img class=&quot;  &quot; alt=&quot;FRIENDS characters&quot; src=&quot;http://stuffpoint.com/friends/image/84677-friends-friends.jpg&quot; width=&quot;691&quot; height=&quot;389&quot; /&gt; FRIENDS[/caption]

I was insanely into FRIENDS that I watched all 10 seasons in 40 days. It did not stop there. I kept watching it again and again. Whenever I felt bored or lonely, FRIENDS was my first choice.

I started reacting like the characters in FRIENDS. Mostly like Phoebe, giving silly explanations, crazy ideas. I could relate whatever that happens around me with some scene. (Like, Joey doesn't share food) :D But the best part is, when people around me are also FRIENDS addicts and they could relate to the same scene. &amp;lt;&amp;lt;Whoopah&amp;gt;&amp;gt; (In Chandler's tone)

I understood how stupid it was after an incident. I was not able to sleep after a long tiring day, because I heard voices of Joey and Phoebe in my head. A small doze of FRIENDS got me to sleep. The next day, I made a rash decision and wiped off all seasons from my disk so that I would focus on something else. But haha. I still miss them. All 6 of them :(
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2013/10/19/f-r-i-e-n-d-s</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2013/10/19/f-r-i-e-n-d-s</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The South Indian in Me</title>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;I have been in Pune in the last 2.5 months and food was not a big problem for me. I enjoy the poha, paav, rottis here. Though I see rice as a part of lunch menu, I rarely take it because I don't wanna eat the so called sambar there. But I am not cribbing. Because I had happy meal everyday. I never *craved* for idli/sambar or a proper lunch with sambar, rasam and curd.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless.....&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2 weeks back, I went to Bangalore for a weekend. Just looking at Adyar Anandha Bhavan got a wide smile on my face. The smell of filter coffee got me high and that is when I realised how much of a South Indian I am..!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2013/09/12/the-south-indian-in-me</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2013/09/12/the-south-indian-in-me</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>So similar & dissimilar</title>
				<description>As a newbie to Python, who before few months was a newbie to Ruby, I felt Ruby &amp;amp; Python so similar in so many ways.
They are both dynamic. The syntax looks similar. And..They both have &quot;print&quot; statement :P When I started writing code in python, I tried everything in the ruby way and my python interpreter threw tomatoes at me for killing the language. Then I realised how good a Ruby programmer I was :P

Method definitions start with def. But they don't end with &quot;end&quot;. Python code is so beautiful. Well indented. Spaces convey a lot.

Return statement is optional in ruby. The value of the last evaluated expression is returned implicitly. But in python, methods don't return anything unless you explicitly &quot;return&quot; something.

In Ruby I often do something like, &lt;strong&gt;print &quot;something&quot; if condition. &lt;/strong&gt;But I truly miss this in python.

Comparing to RubyGems, pip and easy_install are equally good package managers.

Figuring out the python equivalents of my frequently used ruby methods was not that hard.

&lt;strong&gt;inspect&lt;/strong&gt; in ruby is equivalent to __dict__ .

Pry pry pry. Without you, I would have been devastated. Pdb is here to save me here!

One big disappointment is there is nothing like DjangoCasts(unlike RailsCasts) :( But djangodocs provide a very clear documentation.

My experience with python is so far so good. I will definitely add more as and when I explore. :)
</description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2013/06/15/so-similar-dissimilar</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2013/06/15/so-similar-dissimilar</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>What is TWU?</title>
				<description>45 days in Heaven.. Well narrated by one of my friends!
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2012/10/22/423</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2012/10/22/423</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Visualizing Future</title>
				<description>All of us get dreams when we sleep. Not everyone remembers it. And even if we remember, we remember only 5% of it. I've heard people saying dreamy sleep implies disturbed sleep. But, my sleep is incomplete without dreams.. I love sleeping because of the dreams I get.

[caption id=&quot;&quot; align=&quot;aligncenter&quot; width=&quot;480&quot;]&lt;img title=&quot;Dreams&quot; src=&quot;http://tsuganthi.files.wordpress.com/2012/06/dreaming-1721.jpg?w=300&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;480&quot; height=&quot;319&quot; /&gt; Wanna learn more about Dreams..[/caption]

You may call me crazy. But most of my dreams come true. I get solutions to most of my confusions, in my dreams. If I meet someone new, I often get dreams describing how close I'm gonna get with that person.

I once had a dream like a friend of mine(say Alice), inviting me for her wedding. When I woke up, mom says Alice's parents came home for inviting us for her wedding! How weird is that?

Another day, I had a dream like my friend romantically involved with a guy.. That night she calls me and tells that she is in love with him!

I saw my sister in a new house, celebrating house warming.. In two days, my dad told that my sis has got a new home.

Recently, when I took a nap, I visualized one of my friends dressed up like a bride and inviting me to her place. When I woke up, I found that she was getting engaged on that same day!

And a lot more dreams I've had are even more crazy..the food I'm gonna have, the color of dress someone is gonna wear..etc.

My intuitions are not any less comparing to these crazy dreams.I hear something in my head before I lose something. My pen drive, N72 mobile phone, umbrella &amp;amp; even my slippers. Crazy..

I dont understand the scientific reason behind it. But I strongly believe that Mind has the capacity to visualize future.

Its not just me. All of us get dreams. But we forget them,mostly. If your dream is not about something that you already know, it sure has something to do with your future. If you remember your dreams, dont just ignore them. Think about it. If you see something that you dont like or dont want, try to avoid it in real life. :)
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2012/06/25/visualizing-future</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2012/06/25/visualizing-future</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Live like a Swimmer</title>
				<description>&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;aligncenter&quot; src=&quot;http://www.westernmainekids.org/wp-content/uploads/2012/02/cartoon-swimmer1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;169&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kick to move forward..&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Push the obstacles on your way&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Relax. You wont drown..&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Live Life like a Swimmer :)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2012/06/25/live-like-a-swimmer</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2012/06/25/live-like-a-swimmer</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>The Unavoidable!!</title>
				<description>Stranger: Hi.. What do u do?

Me: Finished BE in SSN, Chennai.

Stranger: Oh.. SRM? Good good..

Me: NOOO!! Its SSN. HCL Shiv Nadar's institution!!

&lt;em&gt;Stranger looks at me like I'm a dumb loser&lt;/em&gt;

Stranger: Hmmm. Ok. Some college in Chennai.. Got placed?

Me: Yea. Placed in ThoughtWorks.

Stranger: Oh.. Good. But.. dint u get into CTS or TCS?

Me: (I don't wanna live on this planet anymore)

This is how my intro ends up like, most of the time.. :( :(

But, when suddenly a random stranger appears and says.. &quot;Hey thats cool.. Great going kiddo..&quot;, I smile and nod.. Like a boss :D
</description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2012/06/22/the-unavoidable</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2012/06/22/the-unavoidable</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Tag-athon</title>
				<description>I was asked to join this &quot;TAG-athon&quot; by &lt;a href=&quot;http://preethi-baskar.blogspot.in/&quot;&gt;Preethi&lt;/a&gt;.

Here goes the set of rules to be copy pasted...
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:left;padding-left:60px;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rule#1: Put the rules on your blog.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt; Rule#2: Every person tagged should tell 11 things about themselves,Answer the questions asked by the one that tagged you and Tag few other people and ask them few different questions.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt; Rule#3:Let the people whom you tagged know you've done so.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt; Rule#4: Don't tag anyone who's been tagged before.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt; Rule#5: Really do tag 11 others, don't go all ''if you want to take this tag''.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
11 things about me..
1) Being a gemini, I cant be just the same to everyone around me. Who I'm depends on who you are.
2)  Most ppl call me a perfectionist. Yea. I am one.
3) I believe in my intuitions. My intuitions work most of the time.
4) I am an independent person. I hate taking &quot;NO&quot; for an answer. So, I dont ask help from anyone if I doubt that the answer may be no.
5) I dont beleive in love at first sight. Love can only happen after knowing each other..their likes and dislikes.
6) I dont blindly believe whatever I hear. I listen to both sides of a story before making conclusions.
7) I love eating. But a little conscious about the number of calories it adds to me :P
8) I love hanging out with friends..visiting new places..doing adventurous stuff.
9) Yes I am a chatterbox. But theres a lot of unspoken words deep down in my heart..
10) I dont regret for anything. &quot;All for the best&quot;. I learn from my mistakes.
11) I'm a dreamy person. A lot of random thoughts keep running in my mind almost always.

Hfff! It was so hard for me to blabber 11 things about me. Now, its time to answer Preethi's questions.

1. Your views on God , spirituality , ghosts and athma .
I believe in the uniqueness of God. I am spiritual but not religious. I pray to God whenever I feel like.. I like visiting hindu temples for the architecture and Churches for silence.
I believe in the immortality of souls(athma). They are everywhere. But we cannot feel them because of their low energy level.

2. What makes your life meaningful?
Trying to keep my friends and family happy makes my life meaningful.

3. The best ways to tackle anger and detest.
I dont talk when I'm angry. Because, anger makes you do stupid things which you don't mean to do.
If I hate someone, I ignore whatever they say :P

4. How do you visualize yourself in another 10years.
After 10 years.. I visualize myself as a woman with happy family and successful career.

5. What remains as your far-fetched dream till date?
To take a day off from my routine and stay cool with no responsibilities, no tension.. Havent had any such day so far. :(

6. Something that makes you proud or stays as your identity.
My high energy level.. :D

7. How do you connect with me?
Both of us do not run away from responsibilities. Whatever crazy plan(bunking classes, movies) I make, I know that you will be in for it :P
Now, its my turn to ask few questions:

1) Do you like visiting new/strange places?

2) If given a chance to relive some phase of your life, what would you choose?

3) Whats the best thing that has happened to you so far?

4) Name one person who made a strong impact in your life

5) What are your passions?

6) If given a week off, Where would you go, What would you do?

7) Have you ever felt like you are way too different from the people around you?

Tagging few of my friends now..

&lt;a href=&quot;http://frivolousdrifts.blogspot.in/&quot;&gt;Sindhu&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://pramodhn.blogspot.in/&quot;&gt;Pramodh&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://krisenigma.blogspot.in/&quot;&gt;Sri Krishna&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;https://arunsag.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;Arun SAG&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://gayathrisrinivasan.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;Gayathri&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;a href=&quot;http://karthikishere.wordpress.com/&quot;&gt;Karthikeyan &lt;/a&gt;
</description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>enthudrives.me/2012/03/08/tag-athon</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">enthudrives.me/2012/03/08/tag-athon</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
